<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jasonelle</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jasonelle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/android-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/android-privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Jasonelle organization built the Jasonelle app. This SERVICE is provided by Jasonelle organization at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Apple forbid Cordova, React Native, Native Script and similar technologies?</title>
      <link>/blog/apple-review-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 14:27:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/apple-review-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>If you want your app to be inside the iOS ecosystem it must pass the Appstore Review Guidelines. Apple is known to be strict when approving apps. Since Cordova, React Native, Native Script and similars use Javascript, the sections 4.7 and 2.5.2 of the Appstore Review Guidelines and section 3.3.2 of the Apple Developer Program License Agreement are the most relevant to this use case.
Appstore Review Guidelines - &amp;lsquo;2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonette 3 Ideas and Thoughts</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonette-3-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 12:12:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonette-3-plans/</guid>
      <description>Jasonette Beginnings Jasonette was born in early 2016 and made it&amp;rsquo;s public debut in October 2016.
These are the technical hightlights that Ethan defined for Jasonette.
Features  App loads over HTTP: Your app exists 100% as JSON, and loads from the cloud. No more hard-coding. An app in 30 minutes: No kidding, build an app in 30 minutes. Lowest possible learning curve: No programming experience required. There&amp;rsquo;s only one thing you need to know: JSON.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonette 2 Release Date!</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonette-2.0-release-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 22:55:09 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonette-2.0-release-date/</guid>
      <description>On November 6th it will be a whole year since the beginning of this humble project. We made a lot of changes, bug fixes and some new features to the Jasonette code base since Ethan left.
Expect a new release near the second week of November 2019. This will be stored in the https://github.com/jasonelle/jasonelle repository, in the releases tab.
Future plans? After learning the inner workings of the Jasonette code base and a lot of feedback made in the community we discovered that many issues could be solved by simplifyng the code base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Ignacio</title>
      <link>/blog/welcome-ignacio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 12:27:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/welcome-ignacio/</guid>
      <description>Today is a happy day. Ignacio Álvarez (AKA @Panterozo) will be our core maintainer for Jasonette Android.
He will help Jasonelle in the following areas:
 Keep Android code up to date. Improve code and docs to be cleaner and robust. Help resolving Android questions. Fix bugs. Review code in pull requests. Participate in Roadmap definition. Other Jasonelle related tasks.  Jasonelle Team is proud of it&amp;rsquo;s new member and wish him lots of love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason App APK is Ready to be Used</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonapp-apk-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 12:43:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonapp-apk-ready/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to @schweini for asking this in the issue repo (https://github.com/jasonelle/jasonelle/issues/42).
And super thanks to @TakaKeiji for helping building the APK.
Now you can download the APK for the Jason App and start testing your JSONs Apps without using Android Studio.
Download the APK here https://github.com/jasonelle/jasonelle/releases/download/v1.0/jasonapp.apk.
If you need more info about Jason App, please look into the docs. https://jasonelle.com/docs/tools.html#jason-app-.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Year Without Ethan</title>
      <link>/blog/one-year-without-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 11:49:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/one-year-without-ethan/</guid>
      <description>Today marks one year after Ethan left the digital world.
Ethan was a tremendous human being, someone you can trust and have a good conversation of about any topic.
We really want to think that he took a super long vacation and someday will return. We maintain the hopes high.
This is similar to the https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Waiting_for_Godot tragicomedy.
In this day we want to highlight a tweet he wrote in response to this question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonette Old Blog Migrated</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonette-old-blog-migrated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 14:49:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonette-old-blog-migrated/</guid>
      <description>In order to future proof http://blog.jasonette.com/ we migrated the latest build of those blog posts to http://jasonelle.com/jasonette-old-blog/.
It was a complete copy with small modification to fix missing images and links to the old docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonelle in BeerJS Chile, June 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonelle-in-beerjs-june-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 14:27:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonelle-in-beerjs-june-2019/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we presented Jasonelle in the meetup BeerJS Santiago Chile June 2019.
Have lots of wonderful conversations and fun time talking about Mobile Apps in the modern world using Jasonelle.
Hope many more meetups can be arranged in the future!.
If you want to access the code and presentation, all the code and slides are here:
https://github.com/jasonelle/beerjs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonette Old Docs Migrated</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonette-old-docs-migrated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:49:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonette-old-docs-migrated/</guid>
      <description>In order to future proof http://docs.jasonette.com/ we migrated the latest build of those docs to https://jasonelle.com/jasonette-old-docs/.
It was a complete copy with no modifications. So maybe some links could die.
Expect better docs in https://jasonelle.com/docs/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cell.js No Longer Maintained</title>
      <link>/blog/cell-js-is-deprecated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:57:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cell-js-is-deprecated/</guid>
      <description>Cell.js was an amazing web framework created by Ethan. It&amp;rsquo;s main goal was to simplify web development using JSON like structures.
Jasonelle Team decided that no longer will invest time in Cell.js development.
The main reason is the following:
 Jasonelle will be about Mobile App Development. Web development will not be the focus for Jasonelle.
 A framework to be succesfully be adopted, needs a huge amount of work, examples and documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonette 2 development will begin</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonette-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:57:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonette-2/</guid>
      <description>The current version of Jasonette (Android and iOS) will stop to be futher maintained with bug fixes or new features. The reason is that all the time and energy will be focused on a new version of Jasonette.
Objectives  Backward compatible with Jasonette 1. So you don&amp;rsquo;t have to learn anything new. Modular Code. So it&amp;rsquo;s easier to understands what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind scenes.  iOS The first platform to be supported will be iOS since it&amp;rsquo;s the platform that Jasonelle team have better expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/roadmap/</guid>
      <description> The following features are planned for upcoming versions of the Jasonelle components. These are not the only features planned, they are just a taste.
Jasonette 3  Complete Engine Rewrite. Component Modularization. Use Javascript.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonbase New Version</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonbase-new-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:39:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonbase-new-version/</guid>
      <description>Well today I dedicated the entire day working on a new version of JasonBase, since the old one is dead.
You can access and use it now in https://base.jasonelle.com
And of course see the code at https://github.com/jasonelle/jasonbase
Main Differences This is a list of differences.
   Old New     Private Source Code Available in Github   Made in Ruby on Rails Made with PHP and ProcessWire   User and Password No User-Password only Private Link   Full code editor Just a simple Textarea   Only Json supported in input Json and HJson Supported in input   Output non minimized Minimized output   Intended for Production Intended for Testing and Quick Sharing   Made by Ethan Made by CLSource    The focus on the new Jasonbase is only on the code sharing part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason App Is Not Working</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonapp-is-not-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 10:28:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonapp-is-not-working/</guid>
      <description>As we previously said jasonbase.com is down and many projects that depends on it may not be working.
One of such projects is Jason App. Thankfully we could obtain the json before jasonbase.com&amp;rsquo;s death.
In order to keep using Jason App you should compile a new Jasonette project and direct to the file here
https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jasonelle/docs/develop/examples/jasonette/apps/jason-app/index.json
If you correctly compile you should now have a working copy of the Jason App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonbase Is Down</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonbase-is-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 09:30:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonbase-is-down/</guid>
      <description>As some of you may have noticed if you visit jasonbase.com, you will encounter a 500 error.
This was expected since we didn&amp;rsquo;t have any access to the server or the domain configuration.
This means that other pages may dissapear as well like jasonette.com, celljs.org. Since we cannot pay for the servers to continue running.
Alternatives Jasonbase&amp;rsquo;s focus was to make easier to share JSON files, mainly used for Jasonette projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>