<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Jasonelle</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Jasonelle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:49:27 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonette Old Docs Migrated</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonette-old-docs-migrated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 14:49:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonette-old-docs-migrated/</guid>
      <description>In order to future proof http://docs.jasonette.com/ we migrated the latest build of those docs to https://jasonelle.com/jasonette-old-docs/.
It was a complete copy with no modifications. So maybe some links could die.
Expect better docs in https://jasonelle.com/docs/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cell.js No Longer Maintained</title>
      <link>/blog/cell-js-is-deprecated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:57:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cell-js-is-deprecated/</guid>
      <description>Cell.js was an amazing web framework created by Ethan. It&amp;rsquo;s main goal was to simplify web development using JSON like structures.
Jasonelle Team decided that no longer will invest time in Cell.js development.
The main reason is the following:
 Jasonelle will be about Mobile App Development. Web development will not be the focus for Jasonelle.
 A framework to be succesfully be adopted, needs a huge amount of work, examples and documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonette 2 development will begin</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonette-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:57:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonette-2/</guid>
      <description>The current version of Jasonette (Android and iOS) will stop to be futher maintained with bug fixes or new features. The reason is that all the time and energy will be focused on a new version of Jasonette.
Objectives  Backward compatible with Jasonette 1. So you don&amp;rsquo;t have to learn anything new. Modular Code. So it&amp;rsquo;s easier to understands what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind scenes.  iOS The first platform to be supported will be iOS since it&amp;rsquo;s the platform that Jasonelle team have better expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonbase New Version</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonbase-new-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:39:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonbase-new-version/</guid>
      <description>Well today I dedicated the entire day working on a new version of JasonBase, since the old one is dead.
You can access and use it now in https://base.jasonelle.com
And of course see the code at https://github.com/jasonelle/jasonbase
Main Differences This is a list of differences.
   Old New     Private Source Code Available in Github   Made in Ruby on Rails Made with PHP and ProcessWire   User and Password No User-Password only Private Link   Full code editor Just a simple Textarea   Only Json supported in input Json and HJson Supported in input   Output non minimized Minimized output   Intended for Production Intended for Testing and Quick Sharing   Made by Ethan Made by CLSource    The focus on the new Jasonbase is only on the code sharing part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason App Is Not Working</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonapp-is-not-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 10:28:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonapp-is-not-working/</guid>
      <description>As we previously said jasonbase.com is down and many projects that depends on it may not be working.
One of such projects is Jason App. Thankfully we could obtain the json before jasonbase.com&amp;rsquo;s death.
In order to keep using Jason App you should compile a new Jasonette project and direct to the file here
https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jasonelle/docs/develop/examples/jasonette/apps/jason-app/index.json
If you correctly compile you should now have a working copy of the Jason App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasonbase Is Down</title>
      <link>/blog/jasonbase-is-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 09:30:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jasonbase-is-down/</guid>
      <description>As some of you may have noticed if you visit jasonbase.com, you will encounter a 500 error.
This was expected since we didn&amp;rsquo;t have any access to the server or the domain configuration.
This means that other pages may dissapear as well like jasonette.com, celljs.org. Since we cannot pay for the servers to continue running.
Alternatives Jasonbase&amp;rsquo;s focus was to make easier to share JSON files, mainly used for Jasonette projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>